Post, Libby; Papers apap045
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, 1989-2005; Undated; 5; 0.99 cubic ft.
  - Community Walk, 2003 (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 15)
  - State of The State Report, 2003 (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 16)
  - Survey of Needs and Services, 2003 (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 17)
  - V-Ball: The Red and White Party, 2003 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Job Postings, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 18)
  - Ribbon, Button and Lanyard from Capital Pride, 2003; Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Suzanne Westenhoefer, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 19)
  - commUNITY, 2004 February-2005 February (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 20)
  - Committee Information, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 21)
  - Cynthia M. Swadba Profile, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 22)
  - Development Audit Request, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 23)
  - Gays at the Races, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 24)
  - Tulip Fest Information Booth, Undated (Box 3 (5-Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community ), Folder 25)
- Empire State Pride Agenda, 1987-1992; Undated; 6; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series predominantly contains meeting minutes, agendas, correspondences, and other materials related to the Empire State Pride Agenda.
  - Dick Dadey/Executive Director Reports, 1987; 1989; 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 1)
  - Mailing List Information, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 2)
  - Consolidation Information, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 3)
  - Fundraising, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 4)
  - Sol-C-3 Information, 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1989-1992; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 6)
  - Board Membership/Information, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 7)
  - Marketing Plan, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 8)
  - Domestic Partnership, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 10)
  - AIDS Budget/90 Freeze, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 11)
  - Board Correspondence, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 12)
  - Director's Goals and Evaluation Forms, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 13)
  - Bias Bill, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 14)
  - Financial Information, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 1)
  - Nominations Committee, ca. 1991 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 2)
  - Conservative Caucus Letters and Marques Rodriguez Trial, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 3)
  - Events, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 4)
  - Federal Express Receipts, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 5)
  - Legislative Reports, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 6)
  - Lobbying/PAC/org.info, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 7)
  - NYC Re-districting, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 8)
  - PAC Guidelines/ Recommendations, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and Memorandums, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 11)
  - NGLTS' National Lobby Days Report, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 12)
  - Perry Institute, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 13)
  - Updates, Correspondences, Press Releases, and Issues, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights Reports and Diversity Articles, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 15)
  - Multi-Cultural Development, 1992; Undated (Box 3 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 1)
  - Committee Structure, Undated (Box 3 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 2)
  - Empire State Pride Agenda Needs Assessment, Undated (Box 3 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 3)
  - Executive Director Photo, Undated (Box 3 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 4)
  - Proposed By-Laws, Undated (Box 3 (6-Empire State Pride Agenda), Folder 5)